PATRICIA DERIEUX

Phone: 832-525-3582 | Email: patricia.derieux15@outlook.com |The Woodlands, TX 77382 LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/patricia-derieux | GitHub: https://github.com/patty345 Portfolio: https://patty345.github.io/advance-css-professional-portfolio/

SUMMARY

A self-motivated Full Stack Web Developer with IT experience ready to make an impact in the field. Brining 7 years of work experience in IT as an Application Analyst and learned to be communicative, self-motivated, team-oriented, and problem-solver.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Git, GitHub, Azure DevOps, Heroku, VS Code, ServiceNow, MongoDB, Jason Web Token, ReactJS, Express

PROJECTS

Park Finder https://github.com/patty345 | https://patty345.github.io/park-finder/

- An easy way to find parks near you.
- Developer, and scrum meetings coordinator
- VS Code / HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Foundation, jQuery, MapQuest, and OpenWeather API

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Application Analyst Perry Homes LLC

selection form.

2018 – Current Houston, TX

- Successfully reduced the user's communication method to our Sales staff when submitting exterior
- Improved team efficiency by using automation.
- Collaborated with a custom development team to improve exterior selections form, and received positive feedback from the stakeholders.

IT Support Specialist Perry Homes LLC

2014 - 2018

Houston, TX

- Supported the distribution and configuration of all employees IT equipment.
 - Collaborated with my support team to accomplish the task at hand.
 - Generated company efficiency by providing new equipment to all employees.

Advanced Repair Agent Best Buy

2013 - 2014

Webster, TX

- Resolved customers' computer problems.
- Providing technical support, and repair services.
- Delivering great customer services as well as repairing computer problems.

EDUCATION

Certificate Full Stack Web Development: Rice University, Houston, TX

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, and ReactJS.

Bachelor of Science Computer Information Systems: University of Houston, Houston, TX